24小时
第三季  第14集
前情提要
反恐局的托尼·阿尔梅达刚刚通知我们
Tony Almeida from CTU has just informed us
他们没法在墨西哥没收这个科迪利亚病毒
that they were unable to confiscate this Cordilla virus in Mexico.
这个叫阿马多尔的人 他现在在哪?
This man Amador, where is he now?
最新证据表明病毒在阿马多尔手上
Latest working theory is that Amador has this virus,
他正在回洛杉矶的路上
and is headed back here to Los Angeles.
我救了你一命 告诉我你知道些什么
I let you live. Tell me what you know.
每次阿马多尔在西海岸做交易的时候
Any time Amador does business on the west coast,
都是通过一个叫阿尔弗斯的人
he washes his deal through a man named Alvers.
阿马多尔怎么和这个阿尔弗斯联系呢?
How does Amador contact this Alvers?
我不知道 我没见过他
I don't know. I've never met him.
喂?
Hello?
马库斯 是我
Marcus, it's me.
我一个小时后到
I'll be there in an hour.
拿到病毒了吗?
Got the virus?
拿到了
Yes.
做好准备
Just be ready.
我会的
I will be.
我要去见朱莉娅 米利肯
I got to go see Julia Milliken.
不行 今晚你必须离她或是艾伦远远的
No. I don't want you to go anywhere near her or Alan tonight.
你以为我怕你吗?
Do you think I'm scared of you?
茱莉娅...
Julia...
我的药
My pills.
不 不要
No, don't.
-你在干什么?  -不要
-What are you doing?  -Don't.
-雪莉?  -这是你唯一的出路
-Sherry?  -This is your way out.
-我们杀了他  -不是
-We killed him.  -No.
有件事你必须要清楚
There's one thing you're going to have to be really clear about,
如果有警察局的人来问话
when the authorities come around questioning you.
就说我没有来过
I was never here.
以下事件发生于凌晨两点至三点之间 均与现实同步
The following takes place between 2:00 a.m. and 3:00 a.m..
木谷尖端海军飞机场
Point Mugu Naval Air Station
我抓到她了
I got her.
-鲍尔探员  -我是
-Agent Bauer.  -Yeah.
我是分局的杰森·卡鲁松
I'm Jason Carusone from Division.
他们会把囚犯护送回反恐局
These men will be escorting the prisoner back to CTU.
她不能离开我的视线
She doesn't leave my sight.
我知道 你可以跟她一起坐领头车回去
I know. You can accompany her in the lead van.
走吧!
Let's go!
我是卡鲁松
This is Carusone.
是的 是的 他就在这里
Yeah. Yeah, he's right here.
埃德蒙兹探员
Agent Edmunds.
是你办公室的克萝伊·奥布莱恩
It's Chloe O'brian from your office.
嘿 杰克 我坐另一辆车
Hey, Jack, I'll take another car.
好的
Okay.
是我 克萝伊?
Yeah, Chloe?
蔡斯 他们知道了
Chase, they found out.
谁知道了什么?
Who found out what?
这里的每个人都知道了安吉拉
Everybody here found out about Angela.
他们都知道她是你女儿
They all know she's your daughter.
什么? 他们怎么知道的?
What? How?
保姆走了 她家里有急事 就把她带到这里来了
The baby-sitter flaked. She had a family emergency and brought her here.
你把安吉拉带到反恐局了?
You brought Angela into CTU?
我还能怎么做?你姐姐出城了
What was I supposed to do? Your sister's out of town.
没有别人了
There is no one else.
你不知道我这几个小时是怎么过来的
You have no idea what I've been through in the past couple of hours.
好 好 好
Okay, okay, okay.
克萝伊 谢谢你帮我处理
Chloe, thank you for covering.
非常感谢 但是安吉拉现在在哪?
I appreciate it. But where is Angela right now?
她和马尔西在楼下等你回来
She's downstairs with Marcy until you get back.
金知道了吗?
Did Kim find out?
克萝伊 金知道了没有?
Chloe, did Kim find out?
是的 是的 金知道了
Yes, yes, Kim found out.
她什么反应?
How did she react?
噢 天哪 蔡斯 我想她有点生气
Uh, Gosh, Chase, I think she's kind of pissed.
好吧 听我说 我马上就回反恐局
All right, listen. I'm coming back to CTU right now.
我会处理好一切的
I'll take care of everything.
再见
Bye.
情况是这样的:
Here's the situation:
我们认为迈克尔 阿马多尔拿了科迪利亚病毒
we believe Michael Amador is in possession of the Cordilla virus.
他应该正往洛杉矶赶来 或许已经到了
We believe he is either headed to Los Angeles or he's here already.
我们估计他有足够的病毒 能摧毁一整个大都市
We estimate he has enough of the pathogen to take out a major metropolitan area.
我们唯一的线索就是尼娜·迈尔斯 她正在被带回来的路上
Our only lead is Nina Myers, who's being brought back to CTU right now.
她认为阿马多尔正赶来洛杉矶同一个人见面
She thinks Amador is meeting with a man here in Los Angeles
他的名字叫马库斯·阿尔弗斯
by the name of Marcus Alvers.
亚当对他做了些调查
Adam's done a workup on him.
我们掌握了些背景信息 但是没有信息能确切表明他今天就在洛杉矶
We have some background, but there's nothing that places him definitively in Los Angeles today.
就这些?
That's it?
国际警察组织那边呢? 他们有什么线索?
What about Interpol? What do they have on Alvers?
我们的数据追踪有点滞后
Our data tracking's a little behind,
所以我们还拿不到那份报告
so we weren't able to access that report.
为什么会滞后呢?
Why are we behind?
我受伤的时候我们没有更新与欧洲的联系记录
We didn't update the European contact logs while I was down.
米歇尔,
Michelle
你是名出色的探员
you were the ranking agent.
我以为欧洲不是重点
I didn't think Europe was a priority.
显然是的
Obviously it was.
那时发生了很多事
There was a lot going on at the time.
好吧
All right.
回到工作吧
Let's get back to work.
今晚剩下的时间我们要处理一下之前的失误
And let's try to ease up on the mistakes for the rest of the night
有上百万的生命掌握在我们手中啊
as there are millions of lives depending on us.
米歇尔...
Michelle...
进来
Come.
我刚和反恐局的人谈了下
I just got off with CTU.
有关病毒的情况怎么样?
What's the status on the virus?
嗯 不是很好
Well, it's not good.
目前有限的情报证实了原来的猜测
The limited intelligence they have supports their original suspicion.
病毒正在朝洛杉矶来
It's on its way to Los Angeles.
大卫 可能已经在洛杉矶了
David, it may already be here.
那我们要做好准备以防他们将目标锁定其他城市
Then we should be prepared in case they target other cities.
我们在保护区的市民已经收到警报了
Our people in the security envelope have been alerted.
相信我 一切尽在掌握
Trust me, it's being handled.
你现在为什么不去休息一下呢?
Now, why don't you try and go get some rest?
有我盯着
I'm on this.
总统先生
Mr. President,
帕默尔夫人想见您
Mrs. Palmer's here to see you.
请让她进来
Send her in, please.
提醒他们注意
Start waking people up.
通知必要的内阁成员开会:
Set up a conference call with the appropriate cabinet members:
国土安全局 联邦调查局
Homeland Security, FBI,
国家卫生服务中心
National Health Services.
我们需要所有人都行动起来
We're going to need everyone on this one.
是的 总统先生
Yes, sir.
韦恩?
Wayne?
雪莉, 我叫你来是帮忙
Sherry, I asked you here to help me,
而不是让事情变得更糟
not make things worse.
我不想让你去艾伦·米利肯家
I did not want you going to Alan Milliken's house.
好 放心 大卫 我没去
Well, relax, David. I didn't go there.
-你没去?  -没有
-You didn't go?  -No.
我们在通电话的时候
When we spoke on the phone,
你说必须得要亲自和朱莉娅谈谈
you told me it was crucial that you speak to Julia in person.
是的 不过我改变主意了 我 我和她通过电话了
Yes, and I changed my mind. I-I spoke to her over the phone.
谈了什么?
About what?
关于凯利失踪的事情
About Kelly's disappearance.
我问她是否可以查一下艾伦的手机
I asked her if she would check Alan's cell phone and
看有没有最近的通话记录
see if there were any recently made calls.
然后呢?
And?
她不愿意
She wouldn't do it.
你不会接受一个拒绝的答复的 雪莉
You don't take no for an answer, Sherry.
你还有什么瞒着我?
What aren't you telling me?
没有 大卫 我发誓
Nothing, David, I swear.
我们打完电话后你如果不是去了米利肯家那你去哪儿了?
What have you been up to since we last talked if you weren't at Milliken's?
打电话
Making calls.
你可以在这里打啊
You could have made them from here.
是的 但我没有
Yes, but I didn't.
我把车停在路边
I parked on the side of the road,
然后我开始打电话因为我等不及了
I started making calls because I didn't want to wait.
我告诉过你我们还有一线希望
I told you we have a small window of opportunity here.
我想先揭穿真相
I wanted to exploit the fact that Milliken may not have had time
趁着米利肯还来不及掩盖他抓了凯利这件事
to cover his tracks when he had someone grab Kelly.
好吧
All right.
我还有其他事要忙
I have other things to attend to.
好吧
Okay.
还有其他事吗?
Is there anything else?
没有
That's it.
你好啊 尼娜
Hello, Nina.
带她去819号审讯室
Take her to interrogation 819.
是 长官
Yes, sir.
安全措施怎么样?
What's the security configuration?
别担心 杰克 我们能搞定尼娜
Don't worry about it, Jack. We're handling Nina.
瑞恩 你知道她的能耐
Ryan, you know what she's capable of.
这不是你现在要担心的问题
That's none of your concern right now.
我要送你去做医疗检查
I'm sending you to medical to get checked out.
我没事
I'm fine.
我不这样认为
I don't think you are.
怎么回事?
What's this about?
我们找到你注射海洛因的证据
We found evidence you've been injecting heroin.
告诉我我该滚开 杰克
Tell me I'm off here, Jack.
告诉我是我弄错了
Tell me I'm wrong.
恐怕没有吧
I didn't think so.
瑞恩 我没有走错一步
Ryan, I haven't missed a step.
我很好
I'm fine.
我也得替我自己考虑
I have to cover my ass.
-我要带你去做检查  -你在浪费时间
-I need to get you checked out.  -You're wasting time.
-金  -嗯?
-Kim.  -Yeah?
我想你应该想知道你爸爸回来了
I thought you'd want to know your dad's back.
蔡斯呢?
What about Chase?
他几分钟后到
Uh, he's a few minutes behind.
谢谢
Thank you.
金
Kim.
爸爸
Dad.
噢 上帝 嗨!
Oh, God. Hi.
她被抓来了
She's here.
我知道 宝贝 我知道 来
I know, sweetheart. I know. Come here.
听我说 我要去向查佩尔汇报情况
Look, I have to debrief Chappelle.
待会见 好吗?
I'll see you in a minute, okay?
爸爸 我知道你染上毒瘾了
Dad, I know about your drug problem.
你为什么不告诉我?
Why didn't you come to me with this?
来
Come here.
来这儿
我很抱歉 宝贝
I'm sorry, baby.
对不起
I'm sorry.
我处境很尴尬
I was embarrassed.
而且这不是你的问题 现在也不是
And it wasn't your problem, and it still isn't.
我不想让你担心
I didn't want you to worry.
戒掉了吗?
Well, is it over?
还没有
No, not exactly.
我想我需要一个戒毒疗程 寻求帮助
I think I'm going to have to go into a program, and get some help.
-真的很抱歉  -没关系
-I'm so sorry.  -It's okay.
查佩尔让我去医疗室做检查
Chappelle wants me to go into the clinic and get checked out.
-我们待会再谈这个 好吗?  -好的
-We'll talk about this later, okay?  -Okay.
别担心
Don't worry.
-我爱你  -我也爱你
-I love you.  -Me, too.
好吧
Okay.
杰克
Jack.
很高兴看到你回来
I'm glad you're back.
没有你在我们很不顺利
It's been difficult without you.
谢谢 克萝伊
Thanks, Chloe.
-蔡斯  -嗯
-Chase.  -Yeah.
-我想和你谈一谈  -好吧
-Need to talk to you.  -Okay.
去我办公室谈怎么样
Why don't you take a few minutes and come to my office.
好的 当然可以
Yeah, sure.
米利肯先生?
Mr. Milliken?
米利肯先生? 噢 天哪
Mr. Milliken? Oh, my God.
米利肯夫人!
Mrs. Milliken!
快来!
Come quickly!
快!
Quickly!
嘿
Hey.
你的手怎么样了?
How's the hand?
没事
It's fine.
查佩尔是怎么知道的?
How'd Chappelle find out?
我不知道 这不重要了
I don't know, it doesn't really matter.
外面发生什么事了?
What's going on out there?
阿尔梅达要审问尼娜
Almeida's going to be interrogating Nina,
我会通过连线看的
and I'll follow it from a feed.
好 很好
Okay, good.
让托尼加强守卫戒备
Make sure Tony puts double security on the doors.
一有消息马上告诉我
Get back to me as soon as she gives you anything.
鲍尔探员 按住这里
Agent Bauer, keep pressure here.
好的 谢谢
Sure. Thank you.
杰克
Jack,
你就要知道关于我的一些事了 你不会高兴的起来
you're about to find something out about me that's not going to make you happy.
你在说什么?
What are you talking about?
不好意思 你介意出去一下吗?
Excuse me. Do you mind?
我有个女儿
I've got a daughter.
-女儿?  -我一个月前突然知道的
-A daughter?  -It was sprung on me a month ago.
她的妈妈把她送到我那里 然后离开了
Her mother dropped her off, and she split.
说来话长
It's a long story.
金知道这件事情吗?
Does Kim know about this?
是的
Yeah.
你告诉她的?
From you?
我还没有机会亲自和她谈谈
I haven't had a chance to talk to her myself yet.
你要和她说清楚 蔡斯 你明白我的意思吗?
You square this with her, Chase, you understand me?
妥善处理
Just make that right.
一旦尼娜说了什么就马上告诉我
And get back to me as soon as Nina gives you anything.
我会的
I will.
好了吗?
Are we up yet?
好了 视频已经接入
Yep. Video's piped in,
声音分析 器官监视 图像转录
voice analysis, vitals, transcription.
-全都准备好了  -Nick 收到么?
-We're all set. -Nick, do you copy?
-是的 能听见  -准备开始了
-Yeah, I read you.  -We're ready to go.
好的 现在开始录制到硬盘
All right, recording to hard drive now.
那 托尼来审问吗?
So, Tony's doing this?
对
Yeah.
你不会觉得奇怪?
Is that going to be weird for you?
什么意思?
What do you mean?
他和尼娜不是 不是交往过吗?
Didn't-didn't he and Nina go out?
是
Yeah.
好了吗?
We set?
好了
Yeah.
好的
All right.
把眼睛部位提到高分辨率
I want you to do a hi-res on her eyes.
她累了
She's tired.
也许我们可以捕获些信息
We might be able to pick up a tell.
好的
Okay.
我们之间没什么吧?
So, we all right?
对 没什么
Yeah. We're fine.
好的
All right.
开始吧
Let's do this.
2号监视器提到高分辨率
I got the hi-res on monitor two.
托尼
Tony.
没想到今天会看到你
Didn't know I was gonna see you today.
你知道我们想要什么
You know what we want.
我们需要在迈克尔 阿马多尔释放病毒前找到他
We need to find Michael Amador before he unloads the virus.
我已经把我所知道的都告诉杰克了
I've already told Jack everything I know.
我要你告诉我
Well, I want you to tell me.
首先是杰克 现在又是你
First Jack, now you.
嗯... 这让我想起了什么呢?
Hmm... what does that remind me of?
你告诉杰克 阿马多尔会去联系一个叫马库斯·阿尔弗斯的人
You told Jack that Amador might try to contact a Marcus Alvers.
那 我们在哪能找到阿尔弗斯?
So, where do we look for Alvers?
不错的戒指啊
That's a nice ring.
那个幸运的女孩是谁?
Who's the lucky girl?
不过希望你能做好背景调查 因为
Hope you did a background check, though, 'cause
你也不希望犯两次同样的错误吧
you don't want to make the same mistake twice.
你会回到监狱去
You're going back to prison.
你很有可能会背上叛国罪
There's a good chance you'll be executed as a traitor.
你知道你如果和我们合作的话 你有可能救自己一命
Now you know if you cooperate, you may be able to save your own life,
但是你却在拖延时间
but you're stalling.
这说明你知道什么
Which means you know something
你还以为你可以耍花招
and you still think there's a play you can make,
只不过现在不是时候
only now's not the right time.
说话很尖锐
Very incisive.
但愿你的妻子喜欢你这点
I hope your wife appreciates that about you.
为什么不跟我说说阿尔弗斯呢?
Why don't you tell me about Alvers?
我只知道他只和阿马多尔做生意
All I know is that he works only with Amador.
我并不认识他
I don't know him personally.
我们只能找到一些零散的医疗记录
All we've been able to dig up on him are a few random medical records
用的是他的化名
under one of his known aliases.
他做过膝盖磁共振
He had an MRI on one of his knees,
这里有个抗生素的药方
there's a prescription for antibiotics,
用来治艾滋病的...
treated for HIV...
她的脉搏加快
Her pulse is spiking.
有人和马库斯·阿尔弗斯发生关系没用保护措施哦
Someone hasn't been using protection with Marcus Alvers.
她可能和他发生过关系
She's probably had sex with him.
听着 尼娜
See, Nina,
我隔壁房间的同事告诉我
my colleagues in the next room tell me that something in those
那些医疗记录上有些东西使你担忧
medical records concerns you.
我猜不是因为膝盖吧
I'm guessing it's not the knee.
我来找阿尔弗斯
I'm here to see Alvers.
马库斯.
Marcus
迈克尔.
Michael
旅途怎样?
How was your trip?
很有意思
Interesting.
我还是不明白你为什么要去墨西哥冒那么大的风险
I still don't understand why you risked so much down in Mexico,
为什么不直接来这
why you didn't come here directly.
2.4亿美元让我值得冒这个险
240 million dollars made it worth the risk.
尼娜怎么样?
What about Nina?
如果她没有被炸弹炸死的话
If she wasn't killed by the bomb,
我肯定买主在发现她没有运送病毒之后会好好款待她
I'm sure our buyers took care of her once they found out she didn't deliver the virus.
不管怎样 她都无关紧要了
Either way, she's out of the picture.
但愿如此
I hope so.
她可以揭发我们
She can point to both of us.
在任何人发现我们之前我们已经远走高飞了
We'll be long gone before anyone starts looking.
金.
Kim
听我说 我知道自从我回来后我们还没有说过话
Look, I know we haven't talked since I got back.
是的 没有
No, we haven't.
我知道你在想什么
I know what you must be thinking,
但是你要给我个机会解释啊
but you need to give me a chance to explain.
我不知道该怎么想
I don't know what to think.
听我说 我很高兴你没事
Look, I'm happy that you're okay,
但是这件事...
but this thing...
你有个孩子 蔡斯
you have a baby, Chase.
我们在一起已经三个多月了
We've been together for more than three months,
你竟然还一直瞒着我
and you kept this secret from me.
孩子的母亲是谁? 她什么时候插进来的?
Who's the mother? Where does she fit into this?
这正是我想跟你说的
That's what I want to talk to you about.
我也是一个月前才知道我有个女儿的
I didn't know I had a daughter until a month ago.
你怎么会不知道?
How could you not know?
安吉拉的妈妈和我去年交往了
Angela's mother and I went out last year.
我们已经分手了 分手的时候
Okay, it's over. And when it ended,
她从来没告诉我她怀孕了
she never told me she was pregnant.
一个月前她打电话告诉我她有个孩子
Now she calls a month ago and tells me she has a baby,
我是孩子的父亲
and that I'm the father.
她现在有麻烦 不能照顾孩子
And she's in trouble, and she can't handle it.
我害怕别人会发现
I was afraid to let people find out.
我害怕这会影响我们的关系
I was afraid it was gonna mess us up.
但是你告诉克萝伊了
But you told Chloe.
克萝伊和我姐姐在帮我照顾孩子
Chloe and my sister have been helping me take care of the baby.
她是我的好朋友
She's a good friend.
抱歉 蔡斯?
Excuse me. Chase?
如果安吉拉醒了 你让我告诉你的吧
You wanted me to let you know when Angela woke up.
-谢谢  -不用谢
-Thank you.  -Sure.
金 我也和你一样困惑
Kim, I'm just as confused as you are.
但我只知道我爱你
But all I know is that I love you.
我也开始喜欢上安吉拉
And I'm falling in love with Angela, too.
我必须处理好这个事情
And I need to make this work.
去吧
Go on.
尼娜审问得怎么样?
What's happening with Nina in interrogation?
他们有所发现
They're getting something.
什么?
What?
阿尔弗斯和尼娜的关系可能比我们想象的更密切
The connection between Alvers and Nina might be deeper than we thought.
你最好希望她不是在耍你
You'd better hope she's not just spinning your wheels,
因为她知道怎么和我们周旋
because she knows how to manipulate our interrogation protocol.
托尼知道该怎么做
Tony knows what he's doing.
好吧 我要去见克萝伊
Okay, fine. Look, I need to get together with Chloe.
我要所有有关阿马多尔的调查内容
I need everything that she's got on the Amador investigation.
先别急
Not yet.
瑞恩 你在浪费我的时间
Ryan, look, you're wasting my time.
我迁就你去做了体检
Now, I humored you with the physical.
我们都知道我的血样检测
And we both know that my blood work's gonna come back
会查出有毒品 这已经够了
with trace amounts of opiates, but enough is enough.
检查总部的瑞伊·普拉切基来了
Rae Plachecki from the inspector general's office is here.
她想和你谈谈
She wants to talk to you.
-现在不是时候  -就是现在
-Well, this is not the time.  -Actually, it is.
你要和她谈谈
You'll talk to her,
然后我们再决定你是否可以继续工作
then we'll evaluate whether you can go back to work or not.
来吧
Come on.
瑞伊·普拉切基 这是杰克·鲍尔
Rae Plachecki, this is Jack Bauer.
你知道我们的规矩 杰克 我要问你一些问题
You know the drill, Jack. I'm gonna ask you some questions,
但是我想让你知道 我是站在你这边的
but I want you to know, I'm on your side.
我们只是想证实注射海洛因是你掩饰身份的需要
We just want to establish that this heroin addiction was a necessary part of your cover.
是我掩饰身份的需要
It was necessary to maintain my cover.
可以了吗?
Are we done now?
坐下 杰克
Sit down, Jack.
我是瑞伊·普拉切基
This is Rae Plachecki.
现在时间是凌晨2:31
The time is 2:31 A.M.
这是对杰克·鲍尔 反恐局侦查部部长的审讯
This is the interrogation of Jack Bauer, director of field ops, CTU.
瑞恩·查佩尔在场
Ryan Chappelle is present.
杰克,
Jack
告诉我们你怎样在拉姆·萨拉扎身边掩饰你的身份的
tell us how you established your cover with Ramon Salazar.
我是先和萨拉扎兄弟两人接触
I first came in contact with the Salazars
大约两年前
approximately two years ago.
他们是墨西哥新兴的贩毒集团
They were an up-and-coming narcotic cartel, coming out of Mexico.
那你什么时候见到阿马多尔的?
So, when did you meet Amador?
你在反恐局工作时认识他吗?
Did you know him when you were working at CTU?
说吧 尼娜
Tell me something, Nina,
你知道你这是在做什么交易吗?
what kind of a deal you think you're gonna cut?
你背叛了所有你认识的人
You've betrayed everybody you know,
包括我
including me.
你杀了杰克的妻子
You murdered Jack's wife.
你帮助恐怖分子把核弹偷运到这个国家
You helped terrorists smuggle a nuclear bomb into this country.
你要帮他们把致命的病毒投入人群中
You're helping to unleash a deadly virus into the general population.
我不懂
Help me understand this.
你想要干什么?
What do you want?
做一个谋杀犯对你有什么好处?
What is it you get out of being a mass murderer?
你的脖子在流血
Your neck is bleeding.
道尔顿 发现什么没有?
Dalton, what do you got?
目前 她的反应都是下意识的
So far, the only reactions we're getting from her are subliminal.
如果她再不招供 我们就得在她的器官反应上再下功夫
If she's not gonna say anything, we need to be more plugged in to her vitals.
可以带她去7号审讯室 给她做个被动反应测试
We can take her down to seven, give her a passive response test.
7号审讯室不够安全
Seven's not secure enough.
就让她待在这
She stays here.
理查兹在哪?
Where's Richards?
他正候着
He's waiting.
好吧 让他进来
All right, let's bring him in.
让达伦进来
Send Darren in.
尼娜 我想你没见过达伦·理查兹吧
Nina, I don't think you've met Darren Richards.
他是在你离开后加入我们的
He joined us after you left.
你好 达伦
Hello, Darren.
别介意
Don't take it personally.
他不怎么喜欢说话
He doesn't talk much.
嗯 有些事情我不明白 杰克
Uh, something's not connecting up for me, Jack.
你说你直到二月初才进入萨拉扎集团
You say that you weren't in with the Salazars until early February,
但是你是在12月底开始注射海洛因的
but the first time you started using was late December.
这六周期间你吸毒没有理由啊
That's six weeks of shooting up for the benefit of no one.
我遗漏了什么吗?
Am I missing something?
我想装得更像一个无赖
I was trying to pass myself off as a junkie.
我想充分做好准备
I wanted to be prepared.
什么意思 做准备?
What do you mean, "prepared"?
萨拉扎兄弟一生都在和毒品打交道
The Salazars lived their entire lives in the drug world.
如果我不吸毒
If I couldn't handle the narcotics that went with that territory,
他们会发现我是警察 他们会杀了我
they'd have known I was a cop, and they'd have killed me.
我要处理好这个
I needed to be able to handle it.
是的 这说的过去 但是直到一月份
Yeah, that makes sense, but in January,
当你注射海洛因的时候
when you were putting needles in your arm,
也没有记录显示你和这些人见过面...
you didn't have a meeting on the books with these guys...
也许会要一年 这你们都知道
it could have been a year, for all you knew.
你在说什么?
What are you saying?
我在努力证实你吸毒
I am trying to establish incontrovertible evidence that you did drugs
是为了掩饰身份... 如果我把你刚才讲的提交上去
as part of your cover... if I submit what you just told me,
这是不足以证明你的清白的 杰克
it's not gonna hold up, Jack.
你想让我说什么?!
What do you want me to say?!
我为了混到这些人当中去我吸了毒
I did drugs to get in with these people,
我混进去了!
and I got in with them!
不管有多难 我已经没有吸毒了
And no matter how difficult it's been, I don't use anymore.
听着
Look,
我就这样写 也许会过关
I'll write it up that way, and maybe it'll fly,
但我觉得你可能会有麻烦
but I just think you're gonna have a problem
因为你从来没有告诉过任何人 即使是你的搭档
because you never told anyone, not even your partner.
这有点可疑
That's suspicious.
瑞伊 你知道我的过去
Rae, you know my history.
自从我妻子去世后我一直很痛苦
I've had a very difficult time since my wife passed away.
如果我告诉别人我要为了查案子去吸毒
If I'd told anyone that I was using drugs to develop a case,
他们会误解的
they would have misinterpreted,
我不能冒那个险
and I couldn't afford that risk.
好吧 就看他们怎么想了
Yeah, well, that's what they're gonna do now.
瑞伊,
Rae,
我们就当杰克从一月底开始吸毒
let's put down that Jack started using heroin in late January,
在和萨拉扎第一次见面之后
after the first meeting with Salazar was established.
谢谢你的帮忙 瑞恩
I appreciate what you're trying to do, Ryan,
但是事实不是这样
but that's not what happened.
只是想让我们少打几份报告
Just trying to save us all some paperwork.
我没意见
I'm okay with that.
我有
I'm not.
我是从12月开始吸毒的
I started using in December.
我没有什么好隐瞒的
I've got nothing to hide.
这里需要的是结果
This office demands results,
这就是我能提供的:
and that's what I provide:
结果
results.
好吧
Fine.
我可以回去工作了吗?
Can I get back to work?
还不行 杰克
Not quite yet, Jack.
不 很安全 我们已经拿到了
No, it's secure and we have it.
一切按计划行事
It will be as arranged.
他一小时后到
He'll be here in an hour.
只要在他们释放病毒之前我们有足够的时间离开这个国家就行
Just as long as we have enough time to leave the country before they let this virus out.
请坐
Please be seated.
五个小时前
Five hours ago,
我向公众发表了关于全国恐怖威胁的声明
I went public with a statement that there was a domestic terror threat,
我们以为已经过去了
but it had passed.
但是现在看来还为时过早
And now it appears that that was premature.
女士们先生们
Ladies and gentlemen,
我们现在是否面临病毒释放的威胁?
do we or do we not have a threat of this virus being released?
总统先生
Sir,
恐怕我们还不能确切地回答这个问题
I'm afraid we can't answer that question with any kind of certainty.
你怎么说 哈蒙德先生?
What can you tell me, Mr. Hammond?
线索表明迈克尔 阿马多尔
What few leads we have indicate that Michael Amador has
手握病毒并且已经在洛杉矶
the virus and is in Los Angeles.
出于什么目的 我们不知道
For what purpose, we can't say.
那我们要在洛杉矶做好防范的准备
Then we have to prepare for defensive action here in Los Angeles.
鉴于此 在各大城市
And for that matter, in all of our major cities.
总统先生
Mr. President,
你知道我们国土安全局的立场
you know our position here at Homeland Security.
我们觉得对公众坦白
We think being forthright with the public and
让他们做好准备是正确的选择
making such preparations in the open is the correct course.
还有 我们要估测一下这个方案的不足
Again, we have to assess the downside of that course.
我没意见 总统先生
I have no problem with that, Mr. President,
只是我们要意识到我们正在跟时间赛跑
as long as we realize we are working against a clock.
我希望所有在座的部门制定出内公开的秘密
I want all departments present to work up an open versus covert
牵制策略 30分钟后交给我
containment strategy and report back to me in 30 minutes.
同时 我希望卫生服务发布指导方针
In the meantime, I want Health Services to issue guidelines,
但是只在内部分发行
but only to be distributed internally.
就这样
That is all.
我会在办公室
I'll be in my office.
大卫.
David
请让我们单独谈谈 亚伦
Give us a second, please, Aaron.
好的 先生
Of course, sir.
情报中心刚接到一个电话
Secret Service just received a phone call
是从西洛杉矶警察分部打来的
from the west Los Angeles police department.
艾伦·米利肯死了
Alan Milliken is dead.
什么?
What?
15分钟前尸体在他家里被发现
He was found 15 minutes ago in his home.
所有迹象表明死于心脏病
All signs point to a heart attack.
这不可能
It isn't possible.
但千真万确
Well, apparently, it is.
你说雪莉大约一个小时前在去那里的路上
You told me Sherry was on her way over there about an hour ago.
她改变了主意
She changed her mind.
在车上打了电话
Made some phone calls from her car.
然后直接回来这里
Came straight back here.
大卫 这是她跟你说的吗?
David, is that what she told you?
是的
Yeah.
她现在在哪?
And where is she now?
在休息
Resting.
亚伦 带我去见雪莉
Aaron, take me to Sherry.
是 先生
Yes, sir.
她在这边
She's right this way.
你的轮班还没结束吗?
Hasn't your shift ended?
我留下来了
I stayed on.
我觉得今天有很多困难 我想留下来帮你
I sense it's a difficult day, and I wanted to be here for you.
-谢谢你  -就在这里 先生
-I appreciate that.  -Right in there, sir.
雪莉.
Sherry
大卫.
David
怎么啦?
What's wrong?
艾伦·米利肯死了
Alan Milliken is dead.
什么? 怎么死的?
What? How?
不如你来告诉我?
Why don't you tell me?
你什么意思?
What do you mean?
我跟你说了 我没去那
I told you, I didn't go there.
我知道你告诉我了
I know what you told me.
你坐在车里面给她打了电话
You sat in your car, you made some phone calls,
然后你直接过来了
and you came straight here.
是的 事实就是这样
Yes, and that's the truth.
那你不介意警方检查你的手机
Then you won't mind the police checking your cell phone
以及你今天晚上用过的车吧
and the car you used tonight.
你知道...
You know...
你要我
you asked me
帮你解决这个问题 我照做了
to take care of a problem, and I did.
如果你想让警方检查我的手机通话记录 那么
If you want the police to check phone logs, then
你应该让他们先检查你的
have them check yours first.
记住 你今天晚上打电话给我了
Because remember? You called me tonight.
我因为你才来这里 大卫
I am here because of you, David.
到底发生了什么事 雪莉?
What happened, Sherry?
我去那只是想和朱莉娅谈谈
I went over to the house just to speak to Julia.
艾伦打断了我们
Alan interrupted us.
我们吵起来 然后...
There was an argument and...
他突然心脏病发作
he had a heart attack.
警方会调查的
There's going to be an investigation.
你要说实话
You're going to have to tell the truth about this.
事实救不了我们任何一个
The truth isn't going to save either one of us.
他们将听到的就是我是代表你去那儿的
All they're going to hear is that I was there on your behalf
去阻止艾伦和你竞争总统选举
to prevent Alan from meddling with your presidency,
他是正常死亡
and that he died from natural causes.
那么你觉得纽约时报
Now, how do you think that's going to play out
会在接下来的六个月里怎样报道这件事情吗?
in the New York Times for the next six months?
你对艾伦做了什么?
What did you do to Alan?
实话说 大卫
Honestly, David,
什么也没有
nothing.
什么也没做
Absolutely nothing.
金,
Kim,
我把监控数据接入到了你的系统
I transferred that feed to your system.
你要我现在帮你转进来吗?
Do you want me to pull it up for you now?
好
Yeah.
我觉得她不会向他们招供的
I don't think she's going to give them anything.
我们得自己找到马库斯·阿尔弗斯
We're going to have to find Marcus Alvers by ourselves.
我能做什么?
What can I do?
嗯 我和亚洲那边取得了联系
Um, I followed up on some of those Asian connections,
但是同时 我还有些东西想让你看
but in the meantime, there's something I want you to look at.
-内容很多  -这是什么?
-It's a long shot.  -What is it?
马库斯·阿尔弗斯三年来待过的城市的名单
A list of cities where Marcus Alvers has been in the last three years.
每个地方都只待了几天
Each time only for a couple of days.
也许他是去见某个人
Maybe he was meeting somebody.
把这个和我们资料库里有嫌疑的地方交叉查询
Cross it with the other suspects in our database.
发现了什么就告诉我 好吗?
Let me know what you come up with, okay?
好的
Okay.
听着 我不知道你们为什么要再审问一遍
Look, I don't know why we have to go through this again.
我已经回答了
I already answered that.
怎么了 埃德蒙兹?
What is it, Edmunds?
告诉你尼娜的最新情况
Just wanted to give you an update on Nina.
瑞伊 可以暂停一下吗?
Rae, could you pause that?
她有透露什么关于阿尔弗斯的消息吗?
She give us anything new on Alvers?
没有
No,
除了她可能认识他
other than the probability she knew him personally.
她不愿意合作
She's not cooperating.
我们的人在干什么?
What are we doing?
理查兹在给她用刑
Richards is working on her now.
我觉得这是个错误
I think that's a mistake.
-为什么?  -我觉得不应该让和她没有共事过的人去审问她
-Why?  -I don't think anybody should be in there that hasn't worked with her before,
他不知道她的能耐 会被利用的
doesn't know what she's capable of. She'll manipulate him.
理查兹只是让她承受痛苦
All Richards does is inflict pain.
不可能被她利用的
There's no way for her to manipulate him.
好吧
All right.
你还想忍受多少折磨 尼娜?
How much more of this you want to endure, Nina?
我想就这样了
I think this is about it.
-她刺到动脉了!  -米歇尔 快叫医生!
-She hit an artery!  -Michelle, call medical!
噢 不 她留了太多血 我们得现在就把她送到医务室去!
No, she's bleeding too much. We got to take her there now!
-通知安全中心!  -我们需要医生
-Tell security!  -We need someone from medical.
-这里是819号审讯室  -给她解锁
-Interrogation room 819.  -Uncuff her.
马上!
Now!
雪莉怎么说?
So what did Sherry have to say?
她说艾伦心脏病发作
That Alan had a heart attack.
你相信她吗?
And you believe her?
如果我相信雪莉为保护自己而说的每一句话 那我就是傻瓜
I'd be a fool to believe anything Sherry says to save herself.
但是 谋杀?
But murder?
我无法想象她会那样做
I can't imagine she'd do that.
大卫 在这个关键时刻我们不能被打败
David, we can't allow ourselves to be caught off guard this time.
我们必须做最坏的设想
Now we have to assume the worst.
那么我们也必须设想朱莉娅已经卷入其中
Then we'd also have to assume that Julia was somehow involved.
什么?
What?
噢 噢 听我说
Whoa, whoa, listen.
大卫 抱歉 但是朱莉娅和雪莉不一样
David, I'm sorry, but Julia's not the same kind of person that Sherry is.
等我们查明了全部真相
When we find out all the facts,
我们再继续讨论这个话题吧
we'll proceed from there.
我还要和杰瑞去查看下早上的基本情况
I have to go over the morning brief with Jerry.
好的
All right.
-喂?  -朱莉娅 是我
-Hello?  -Julia, it's me.
韦恩?
Wayne?
我刚从艾伦那里听说 我...
I just heard about Alan, and I...
你一个人吗?
are you alone?
警察在这里
The police are here.
警方正要找我谈话
I'm was just going to speak with one of the officers.
好 告诉我发生什么事了
All right, tell me what happened.
韦恩 事情发生的时候雪莉在场
Wayne, Sherry was here when it happened,
但是她让我不要告诉警察
but she told me not to tell the police.
朱莉娅 我需要你把确切的事情告诉我 好吗?
Julia, I need for you to tell me exactly what happened over there, all right?
我们当时在和艾伦说话
We were talking with Alan.
他变得很激动
He got excited,
然后他开始喘气
then he started to gasp for air.
他开始心绞痛
He gets angina.
于是你打了911 是吗?
So you called 911, right?
不 不是
No, no.
我... 我试图去给他拿药
I-I tried to give him his medication.
你试图?
What do you mean you tried?
雪莉阻止了我
Sherry stopped me.
我要去帮艾伦
I went to help Alan,
但她抓住了我的手
but she grabbed my arm.
我就站在那里
I just stood there.
我 我不能 我不能动
I-I couldn't, I couldn't move.
我... 我...
I... I...
-是我杀了他 韦恩  -嘘 嘘 嘘
-I killed him, Wayne.  -Shh, shh, shh.
仔细听我说 好吗?
All right, listen to me carefully, all right?
我杀了他
I killed him.
打电话给艾伦的律师 什么也不要说
Call Alan's lawyer, and do not say anything,
在他来之前不要对任何人说任何事
anything to anyone until he gets there.
懂了吗?
You understand me?
韦恩 你能来这帮我吗?
Wayne, could you come down here and help me?
不行 请你不要打电话给我
No, and please don't call me.
我会帮你的 朱莉娅 我会的
I will help you, Julia, I will,
但现在我必须与你保持距离 抱歉
but for right now I have to keep my distance, I'm sorry.
不好意思 让一下
Excuse me, coming through.
-快点 在这  -好 移到这边
-Let's move, right here.  -Okay, swing it.
快 快 走!
Come on, come on, let's go!
1 2 3
One, two, three.
颈动脉破裂 进行局部麻醉
Carotid's been lacerated. Start a twilight drip.
是 医生
Yes, doctor.
夹住
Clamp.
稳定血压
Keep steady pressure.
3-0缝合
3-0 silks.
3-0准备
3-0 standing by.
纱布
More gauze.
Gauze.
-打开  -好 夹住
-Got it open.  -Okay, clamp it.
给 医生
Here you go, doctor.
-加压  -是 医生
-Keep the pressure on.  -Yes, sir.
再拿纱布来
Let's get some more gauze in here.
好了 她已经平静下来
Okay, she's under.
你们两个守在这里
I want you two stationed right here.
没有我的亲自指令不得离开
Do not leave unless you hear directly from me.
好 杰克 我奉命问完了
Okay, Jack, those are all the questions I'm obliged to ask.
你如果还有什么要补充的 杰克
If you got anything else you want to add, Jack,
现在就说
now would be the time.
就这么多
That's my statement, as it is.
天哪 托尼
My God, Tony.
尼娜想要自杀
Nina tried to commit suicide.
她用脖子插向理查兹的针管
She jammed her neck into Richards' needle,
动脉破裂
ruptured an artery.
她现在在哪?
Where is she now?
她正在医务室动手术
She's in the clinic being operated on.
谁守在那?
Who's with her?
别担心 杰克 已经给她注射镇定剂了 我看见她平静下来
Don't worry, Jack, she's sedated. I saw her go under.
谁守在那里? 托尼 谁在看着她?!
Who's with her now? Tony, who's with her?!
妈的!
Damn it!
她去哪儿了?
Which way did she go?
封锁大楼!
Lock down the building!
我是瑞恩·查佩尔
This is Ryan Chappelle.
尼娜·迈尔斯逃跑了 还在大楼里
Nina Myers is loose in the building.
封锁大楼 赶快!
Lock it down, now!
尼娜,
Nina,
放下枪
drop the gun
手放头后
and put your hands on your head,
快!
now!
金
Kim.
你在干什么?
What the hell are you doing?
你不想牵扯进来吧
You don't want to be any part of this.
闭嘴
Shut up.
你只要转身
Just turn around
然后离开
and walk away.
如果你现在离开 你不会受到伤害
If you leave now, you won't get hurt.
金.
Kim.
别这样做 尼娜 我发誓 我会毙了你
Don't do it, Nina. I swear to God, I'll shoot you.
你不会杀我的
You won't kill me.
尼娜 妈的
Nina, damn it.
金 退后
Kim, back up.
退后
Back up.
金 回反恐局告诉他们我们找到尼娜了
Kim, I want you to go back into CTU, tell them we got Nina.
-爸爸 听我说 我们需要...  -金 快去!
-Dad, listen to me. We need...  -Kim, go now!
求你了 宝贝 走
Please, baby, just go.
走啊
Go.
你没有什么有用信息了 是吧 尼娜?
You don't have any more useful information, do you, Nina?
我有
I do.
不 你没有
No, you don't.